|     |     |
| --- | --- |

|     |
| --- |
| [**Home**](http://www.peoplebyname.com/)<br><br>Privacy Policy |
| Privacy Policy<br>==============<br><br>1\. **Information Available Through PeopleByName.com**  <br>a) PeopleByName.com aggregates publicly available information from phone books, social networks, marketing surveys, real estate listings, business websites, and other public sources (“Public Information”). This Public Information may be made available to users through the PeopleByName.com website. PeopleByName does not verify and cannot guarantee the accuracy of this Public Information.  <br>b) Personal Information, such as information that You provide to PeopleByName.com or information about Your use of PeopleByName.com is not part of the Public Information available to users through the PeopleByName.com website.  <br>  <br>2\. **Personal Information on Peoplebyname.com**  <br>a) You may use Peoplebyname.com without creating an account. Even without an account, Peoplebyname.com collects information about Your use of Peoplebyname.com website. This may include information about any IP address used to access Peoplebyname.com and Your activity on Peoplebyname.com. Peoplebyname.com uses cookies, or small text files stored on Your computer, to store data about Your visits.  <br>b) Peoplebyname.com collects information that You provide in creating an account at Peoplebyname.com. This may include information such as Your name, address, phone number, email address and or credit card information.  <br>c) Peoplebyname.com allows You to retain and access Your search history on our site. Peoplebyname.com does not share your search history with any third party.  <br>d) Certain features of Peoplebyname.com permit You to edit Your personal information and or payment information.  <br>  <br>3\. **Use and Sharing of Personal Information**  <br>Peoplebyname.com may use Personal Information You provide to PeopleByName.com to create and maintain Your account, to personalize Your experience, and to send periodic email communications relating to our services, such as purchase receipts, account confirmations, and customer service correspondence. PeopleByName may provide your email address to a third party service solely for the purpose of delivering email communications and preventing fraudulent transactions. PeopleByName.com does not sell, exchange, transfer, or give this type of Personal Information to any other company without Your consent.  <br>  <br>4\. **Removing your Personal Information from PeopleByName.com**  <br>You may remove your information from the PeopleByName People Directory by visiting the removal page at [http://www.peoplebyname.com/remove.php](http://www.peoplebyname.com/remove.php)  <br>5\. **Contacting PeopleByName.com**  <br>If You have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at support \[at\] peoplebyname.com  <br>  <br>Effective Date: February 10, 2014 |
|     |

**1,379,043,021** total records available

[**Testimonials** _Read testimonials from real customers who already used our services._ **Read More**](http://www.peoplebyname.com/testimonials.php)[**Webmasters** _Earn 75% comission on every sale you drive to our website. Weekly payouts!_ **Read More**](http://www.peoplebyname.com/affiliates)[**Mobile Version** _Visit us from your smart phone anywhere you are._ **Read More**](http://www.peoplebyname.com/mobile.php)[**Recent Lookups** _Check out the most recent reverse phone lookups on PeopleByName.com_ **Read More**](http://www.peoplebyname.com/recent_lookups.php)

© **PeopleByName** All Rights Reserved. 2010-2024
